Real Estate school; I recommend it to everybody.
I meet people out there, and we talk about "you want to get your real estate license?
Yeah, I think I'll take it online."
Well I'll tell you, my experience was incredible taking it in the classroom.
You know, you're working that 8 - 5 job and you're probably feeling discouraged right now.
Classroom does not have to mean 8 - 5 sitting in the classroom.
It can mean, when you get off work at 5 you go to the classroom and you might be sitting there from 6 - 9 or 10.
Yeah you're going to be a little bit tired, but you know let's load up on the coffee.
Or you might take it, you might ask your, whoever you're working for, can I take off Friday?
Take off every Friday for the next probably two or three weeks.
Because believe it or not, that's how long it takes, about two or three weeks to get your real estate license.
The key is, there's certain course requirements, and so the classroom hours, I mean there's usually four core courses of what you need to take.